Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
DYNAMITE KISS
Let me buy them off you.
Do you take credit?
Who are you?
Just make a direct sale to me
if you're going to sell anyway.
Skip the cutting, harvesting,
and refrigerating.
I'm offering to save you the trouble
of going through all that nasty stuff.
What do you say?
Well…
We're good as long as we get the money.
There we go.
It's fine. Just consider it a freebie.
Mr. Gong…
Hold on.
Let's go get some drinks.
Don't ever show your face to her again.
If you do,
I'll buy all your organs too.
Sorry. My knees just gave out.
EPISODE 5
The end.
Dad, when will that pretty lady be back?
"Pretty lady"?
Your friend who picked me up today.
My friend…
Ms. Yu Ha-yeong?
Can she be your girlfriend?
Why?
She's pretty.
Don't worry about me
and focus on
finding yourself a girlfriend.
It's late. Go on and sleep now.
Put your head on the pillow.
It's all over now.
I'm sorry.
I was just so scared earlier.
Of course, you were.
Who wouldn't be in that situation?
Thank you so much, Mr. Gong.
I'll figure out a way
to pay you back as soon as--
Da-rim, let's just forget
about everything for now
and get some rest.
Let's go home.
All right.
Here.
BANDAGES
-Did you have dinner?
-Not yet.
Did something happen?
No.
That looks delicious. Thank you.
What happened to your wrist?
Oh, this? It's nothing.
-It clearly isn't. Let me see.
-It's really nothing.
Did it happen at the office?
Is that why your team leader
drove you home?
You saw?
Well, you know the loan sharks?
They showed up at the office
and dragged me away.
And you're only telling me this now?
Are you okay?
Mr. Gong followed us and saved me, and…
Da-rim?
-Hey, Go Da-rim.
-Right. Sorry.
He saved me and paid off my debt.
He paid off…
your debt?
I think he paid it off
because it was an emergency.
I need to talk to him tomorrow.
I'm just a nuisance
to all those around me.
Sorry.
I should've been more attentive.
Why would you be sorry?
I'm the one who should be sorry
for making you worry about this.
Anyway, thank you.
This looks delicious.
Do you take credit?
Don't ever show your face to her again.
Thank you so much, Mr. Gong.
Mr. Gong. Mr. Gong.
Mr. Gong, we'll…
Mr. Gong. Mr. Gong?
That's right.
She's a member of my team.
I just did what I had to do
as the team leader.
Most definitely. Okay.
Why is that meeting taking forever?
It's making me anxious.
I hope Mr. Gong isn't being
severely told off because of us.
What if someone gets fired over this?
I'll leave.
I was the one
who left during the broadcast.
Why would you leave?
I'm the one responsible
for the actual accident.
No, you were only there
to cover for me in the first place.
-If anything, I should get fired.
-What if we all get fired?
Excuse me, Mr. Gong?
How'd it go?
Are we all fired?
Why would you be fired?
Don't worry.
Mr. Gong took care of everything.
He did?
"I sincerely apologize
for the trouble caused
by yesterday's live commerce."
"I was much too focused
on our competitor's broadcast
and recklessly assigned it
to an unprepared team."
"I'm very much at fault."
"Why would you apologize, Ms. Gong?"
"A mother shouldn't need to rehearse
changing a diaper."
"Not to mention,
it was utterly unprofessional
for the other host to run out bawling!"
"I believe if anyone is at fault
for tarnishing this company's reputation,
it's the team leader."
I'm sorry to interrupt…
but I believe our company's reputation
has actually improved.
This shows the number of posts
on social media and online mom communities
that mention Natural BeBe
since the livestream.
The majority of them praise Ms. Lee Go-eun
for sharing her story
and Natural BeBe
for its single-mother support program.
We're also trending
across major search engines,
and there has been an outpouring
of online articles.
ADDED IT TO MY CART IMMEDIATELY
RIGHT AFTER THE LIVESTREAM!
Angel Hugs' daily sales
have also increased
by more than ten times the usual.
As you can see,
Natural BeBe's boost in brand image
directly led to increased sales.
The sales during the livestream
may have been low,
but its marketing impact
was far beyond expectations.
"I believe this is what they call
a blessing in disguise."
"What do you all think?
My son isn't too shabby, huh?"
And then everyone went…
Don't go overboard.
When did you do all that research?
You were here until late yesterday,
working on the incident report.
How did you have the time?
He came in very early this morning.
I told you, didn't I?
Innate leadership.
Deep affection for his employees.
That's who Mr. Gong is.
No wonder. I knew I could
put my faith in him from the start.
You know, jerks come in all kinds.
Mr. Gong isn't an ignorant jerk.
He's a learned man,
which makes him a competent jerk.
Yeah, I think I understand.
His every word pisses you right off,
but he's right on all counts.
Exactly.
You got lucky this time,
but it won't happen again.
From now on,
you must get my confirmation
on everything first
and follow my orders at all times.
And don't be stubborn for no reason.
If and when I say no,
it means no.
Do you understand?
-Yes, sir.
Okay.
How strange.
Why did you change your mind?
What do you mean?
You're going to confirm
and sign off on every little thing?
What happened to never bothering you?
You.
Gyeong-min, you…
What about me?
You called me an innate leader.
I think that describes me perfectly.
No matter how much I try not to care
about my team members,
I can't help myself.
I've been losing sleep,
and my heart's been burning up
with passion.
It must be a side effect of my trying
to suppress that innate leadership.
So I came to the conclusion that I should
let my leadership run free while I'm here
if I don't want to fall ill.
It's tiring to be so perfect.
Gyeong-min, I'm tired.
Does the blind squirrel really deserve
such praise for finding a nut?
Damn it.
Mr. Gong is one lucky guy.
It's as if those nuts
all lined up in front of him,
ready to be harvested.
Can you not?
This won't do. We need to eliminate
any chance of them accomplishing anything.
But we can't just let them idle
without giving them any work, can we?
No, we can't.
So we need to send them
where their efforts will go least noticed.
It's a promissory note.
I'll be sure to pay you back 700,000 won
every month.
Won't that be difficult?
You have to pay
for your mother's hospital bills too.
Not at all.
This is something I must do,
no matter what.
Regarding the interest, would keeping it
at the bank interest rate--
Forget the interest.
Just pay the principal.
Are you sure?
How can I collect interest
from a team member?
Mr. Gong.
Did you tell your husband?
Of course.
He wanted me to tell you
how grateful he is for your generosity.
Not about the money,
but the danger you were in.
He could've at least
picked you up from work for a few days
if he knew loan sharks were after you.
Is he always so indifferent?
No, of course not.
My husband isn't like that.
He's just been a bit busy recently.
He's normally very attentive.
I would go so far as to say
that he's too good for me.
How can you say that
when you almost lost all your organs?
You should know what to defend
and what not to.
What counts
is being there when you need them.
This whole situation!
Who was the one who paid to resolve it?
Sorry?
Listen carefully.
Until you pay off this debt,
you're mine, Ms. Go Da-rim.
What does that even mean?
All mine!
Your eyes, brain, lungs, heart, liver,
kidneys, and everything else! All of it!
Are you claiming ownership
over my organs right now?
Speaking of which, your eyes right now.
I don't like them, so look away.
I can't even look at what I want?
Of course not. Because they're mine.
I bought those eyes.
With my money!
Seriously, what's wrong with him?
He's so weird.
Come on.
That's all grease.
It's terrible for your organs.
-That's my lunch.
-No.
I refuse to subject my organs to this.
-A salad?
-Consumption is the quickest disposal.
Okay.
My precious sausage bread…
Change into these.
What? Those look really painful.
I'm okay.
Don't be absurd.
They say your feet are your second heart.
They're a miniature version of your body,
connected to all your organs.
You must wear them
for the sake of the health of my organs.
I don't need to wear these.
My organs are already very healthy.
If you're going to do whatever you want,
then pay off your debt first.
Wait…
-What's that?
-Oh my gosh!
Oh.
I bought some parenting books
and magazines
to keep up with the trends.
-Here. Let me carry it.
-No, I'm fine.
-It's fine. Give it to me.
-No, I'm really okay.
-One, two, three!
-I'm really…
Thank you.
Nothing beats climbing the stairs
to improve your cardiovascular endurance.
You must take them
for the sake of my heart health.
The emergency stairs are over there.
Good luck.
I probably would've been better off
selling them to the loan sharks.
JUN BABY STUDIO
Darn it.
Oh my.
Ms. Yu!
DINO POWER
DELUXE SUPER KING BLAST WING
This is for Jun.
I promised him yesterday
that I'd get it for him.
I'm sorry.
-Let me pay you back.
-No, please don't.
-I'm the one who should be grateful.
-Pardon?
Can I ask you something?
Sure.
I unintentionally found out yesterday
that Jun has never seen his mom before.
He told you that?
Yes.
We separated when he was little.
Oh, I see.
Then, by any chance,
are you seeing anyone right now?
No, I'm not.
Thank goodness.
Thank you so much.
What are you thankful--
I'm suddenly so hungry.
Since I bought this robot for Jun,
can you buy me a bowl of jjajangmyeon?
This is a family park the company
has been running for over 20 years
as part of its corporate
social responsibility initiative.
There's a playground for the kids
over there.
We also built a fountain plaza
and a nature learning center
to make it a fun and relaxing
family-friendly park.
It's huge. This place is so nice.
I know, and even the admission is free.
How did I not know about this place?
But I don't see many visitors.
As of late,
corporate support has been minimal.
That's why promotion is limited
and the facilities are showing their age,
which has led to a steady decline
in visitors.
Then why did they build it
in the first place?
So, what are we here to do today?
My back is killing me.
Are we being punished
for screwing up the livestream?
It hasn't even been a month
since I got my laser treatment.
What if it all goes to waste?
We should be thankful
we still have our jobs.
This is nothing compared to giving birth.
Yeah, you're totally right about that.
I passed out
when I was giving birth to my oldest.
I was in labor for 12 hours,
and my kid's head got stuck in my pelvis
because it was so big.
They had no choice
but to use a vacuum extractor,
and my kid's head is still dented.
I cried so much
about my kid having a cone-head.
I don't even remember the pain.
What about you, Da-rim?
How was it for you?
What?
For me…
What was it again?
What did Mom say about my birth again?
I was in labor for a full day and a half,
but in the end,
they had to do a C-section--
-What's wrong?
-You poor thing.
Jun better be
the world's greatest son to you.
-What?
-That's the greatest injustice.
You go through all that labor pain
just to have surgery.
But isn't it just amazing?
As soon as you see your baby,
you forget all about the pain.
I know, right?
You're so right.
He was so adorable with such fair skin.
I thought I gave birth to an angel.
Your newborn was adorable with fair skin?
They're all red and wrinkly.
You know, it sometimes sounds like
you've never raised a child.
-What?
-Da-rim.
There was also that diaper incident.
You've never raised a kid, have you?
What are you talking about?
I fed and bathed him myself.
Don't lie to us. We can just tell.
Your hands look like
they've never done hard work.
Just look at that soft and smooth skin.
Oh no.
Have I been exposed?
I bet her loving husband
changed every diaper
and made sure
she didn't even lift a finger.
And the baby
probably takes after his handsome father.
That's probably why she thought
he looked like an angel.
-You know how it goes.
-Loving husband, my ass.
-I should get out of here.
-Of course, her husband is so handsome.
-My back is killing me.
-I'd like to see his handsome face.
I'm telling you, Nan-suk.
-He's ridiculously handsome.
-Really?
-Yeah, he is.
-Goodness gracious.
How can someone be so lucky?
And she gave birth to a son. How perfect.
That was a close call.
I should just shut up if I don't know.
Do you want some help?
Really?
-Thank you so much.
-Not at all.
You must've been uncomfortable.
Just hold on a second.
Here we go.
That's it.
You're so cute.
-All done.
-Oh gosh.
-Thank you.
-It was nothing.
I actually hurt my hand.
You're really good at this.
I practiced a lot while watching videos.
But I noticed you were using
a foreign brand of diapers.
A Korean brand called Natural BeBe
also sells excellent diapers.
I know, but this brand donates
part of its proceeds
to environmental protection.
The environment has become
my biggest concern after giving birth.
When you realize that this world is
where your child will grow up and live in,
your mindset shifts.
I see.
Seeing myself change like this
makes me realize that motherhood
is pretty amazing.
It's just as cool as the Grandfather Tree
in my neighborhood.
What's that?
"Gong Ji-hyeok"?
Wait.
What are you doing?
Mr. Gong, your name is here.
"Gong Ji-hyeok Tree."
GONG JI-HYEOK TREE
APRIL 5, 2002
Here we go.
All done.
GONG JI-HYEOK TREE
APRIL 5, 2002
Okay.
Look over here.
One, two, three.
So it's a tree you planted
with your mother.
It must bring back memories.
I just planted it
and never took care of it,
but it grew up strong all on its own.
You should
bring your mother here sometime.
I'm not sure
if that'll be possible.
She's at the same hospital as your mother.
She's been unwell for a long time.
So that's why we ran into each other
at the hospital last time.
It must've been tough for you as well.
I hope she gets better soon.
Oh, then how about
I take a picture of you with it
so you can show it to your mother?
I'm sure she'll love it.
Stand there.
I'll take the picture.
Stand right there.
That looks good.
Maybe you should pose.
That's great,
but how about we go for something cute?
Cute?
Yes, cute.
That's pretty cute,
but maybe add a cheek heart?
Or an ear heart,
a bear heart, or a cat heart.
Or maybe a giant one like this.
Stop laughing and do it.
Your mom will love it.
Here we go.
Get ready.
He really is very handsome.
Oh, right.
Are you ready?
One, two, three.
So cute.
Next. One, two, three.
Great.
One, two, three.
What? What's wrong?
-What happened?
-Bee! A bee!
-There's a bee. A bee!
-A bee? Where?
Where?
It's not a bee. It's a ladybug.
What on earth is so terrifying
about this tiny little thing?
Well…
I experienced
a traumatic hornet sting in the past.
Don't laugh.
I said don't laugh.
You didn't even bat an eyelash
in front of organ harvesters.
Childhood scars last a long time.
That's a childhood scar?
-Don't make fun of me.
-Right, I'm so sorry.
-Wait, there's a bee!
-Where?
Don't laugh.
Wait, Mr. Gong, it's a real bee this time.
I'm not lying. Oh no.
You're going to get stung.
Stop it!
-Let's go catch it!
-Stop it!
I told you to stop.
It's been a while
since we came here together.
How's your mother doing?
She has her ups and downs.
I hope she gets better soon.
Recently,
I've been thinking a lot about the days
when she was the executive director.
She built this park,
ran a tree-planting campaign,
and even raised funds
for environmental protection.
I took great pride in my work back then.
It sounds like Mr. Gong's mother
did a lot of good.
But now, they've all been discontinued,
and I heard they're planning to
sell this park as well.
Why?
Because a company's goal
is to maximize profit.
Without a clear guiding philosophy
at the helm,
social responsibility activities
fall to the wayside.
That's too bad.
It would've been nice
if they could've actively promoted
the tree-planting campaign
and this park from the get-go.
Pardon?
If it's a similar-quality product,
moms are bound to favor companies
that actively engage
in environmental protection efforts.
Since this is the world
their children will grow up and live in,
they want to do their part.
Why does it have the same name as me?
GONG JI-HYEOK TREE
Because it was planted for your sake.
I named it after you, wishing it'd grow
tall and strong alongside you,
while making the world a cleaner place.
Because you're bound to be happier
in a cleaner world.
Then we should plant a lot of trees.
So everyone can be happy.
Ta-da.
Mom, do you remember?
That's the tree we planted.
This is how much it's grown.
You're right, it has.
Right?
I used to live life
with such passion and energy.
It was all in vain.
I don't even know
what's left of it anymore.
Yeah, you do.
You have me.
You have your son right here by your side.
Speaking of which,
I'm actually trying to turn that dream
you worked so hard for
into reality.
So you need to get well quickly
and watch me do it.
Okay?
Stop moving.
You're being exceptionally sweet today.
Well, you've been through a lot.
What do you mean?
When you gave birth to me,
you must've felt so wronged
getting that surgery
after going through all that pain.
I'm apologizing for that now.
Am I finally being rewarded for that now?
Wow, you really took your time with that.
I heard the moms talking at work.
Just hearing about it
sounded so terrifying.
How did you endure all that pain?
-When you endure all that pain,
-Yeah?
you end up with a daughter like this.
So why wouldn't you?
I'd gladly give birth to you again
if I had to.
You're just too cute.
Go on.
-Stay still, ma'am.
-Okay.
-Careful.
-That tickles.
Just getting home?
Yeah.
You're late.
I went to see my mom.
What about dinner?
Hey, do you have ramyeon?
That looks so good.
Bon appétit.
-Is it good?
-Yeah.
I guess Jun went to bed early.
Yeah, they apparently had a race
at daycare today.
He's knocked out.
He's such a cutie pie.
It's so spicy.
How's your mom doing?
I called her earlier.
The doctor said
she's recovering quickly
with little to no long-term complications.
That's a relief.
Hang in there.
Seeing her get better
gives me all the energy I need.
Even work is fun.
Did your team leader say anything
about the money?
He just wants the principal.
You know,
when he was saving me
from the loan sharks,
he was super charismatic,
saying things like, "Do you take credit?"
But it turns out he's terrified of bugs.
This tiny ladybug made him go frantic,
and he was all,
"Bee! There's a bee!"
He was freaking out.
Isn't that hilarious?
Was it that funny?
What? I thought it was.
You don't think so?
I guess. Sure.
So funny.
This quarter,
we plan to focus on
corporate image marketing.
We're planning a global marketing campaign
with international celebrities.
What do you think, Mr. Gong?
I'm not sure.
Wouldn't environmental issues
be a better fit for a global campaign?
-Are you serious?
-Hold on.
Go on. What exactly do you propose?
We could revive
our discontinued tree-planting campaign
to highlight and promote
Natural BeBe's long-standing commitment
to environmental protection
since its founding.
It's not a bad idea
for the domestic market.
But at the brink of global expansion,
we first need a solid corporate image--
That's what makes it
all the more compelling.
The global trend is pursuing
environmental protection,
social responsibility,
and transparent management
through ESG management.
Furthermore, ESG indexes
have recently started to be reflected
in the International Financial
Reporting Standards.
This indicates that companies
can now attract global investment
based on their contributions
to environmental protection
and social responsibility.
Is there anything more important
than securing funds when it comes to
business expansion?
You make a good point.
I want to see a detailed proposal
from both of you by next week.
I'll decide after you present.
A competitive pitch?
Against the marketing team, at that?
Yes.
Shouldn't experts with real experience
handle that?
You scolded us for being reckless,
but you're even more reckless than we are.
Tell me about it.
We're busy raising kids,
so we don't know anything about trends.
I believe this project
should be grounded
in the genuine sentiments of mothers,
not in fleeting trends.
That way,
we'd be able to deliver a clearer
and more heartfelt message
from a parent's perspective.
Also, this idea came from our team,
so it's only right that we see it through.
From our team? Who?
Ms. Go Da-rim.
Smarter than appearances suggest.
-Really?
-When did you think of that?
I did?
Your talk with the CSR team leader.
Oh, that?
Brief the team on it
and lead the brainstorming session.
Yes, sir. I will.
Let's be sure to win…
this presentation.
Okay.
Thank you for the praise earlier.
It feels really good to hear
that I helped out the team.
I praised you?
You, Ms. Go Da-rim? When?
You said I was smart.
I was commenting on a smart brain.
I never said you were smart.
It seems you took it the wrong way.
What I praised
was this brain here.
And who does it belong to?
Me.
I guess it was self-praise.
Of course.
-A photographer?
-Yeah.
I'm working on an ad concept,
and I remembered you said you were
preparing for a photography exhibition.
I thought you might know someone talented.
It got canceled.
My dad doesn't want me to do it.
Oh yeah? Well, that's too bad.
Wait.
I do know a photographer.
LEVER DU SOLEIL
KIM SEON-U
What do you think? Aren't they so nice?
Yeah.
It's natural and warm.
Right?
He's a warm person.
He's warm-hearted and speaks warmly too.
And his face
is just full of so much warmth.
I think he'll fit the vibe
we're going for.
Give me his number.
I worked my butt off
to uncover this photographer.
He was completely hidden
like some dinosaur fossil.
I guess you want something in return.
Let me in on that project.
-The pressure's giving me indigestion.
-Me too.
I'd much rather be weeding.
I think the big budget
makes it that much worse.
So much pressure.
My goodness, look who it is.
It's our rival team.
So? Is your presentation
coming along well?
It's our first ad, so it's a bit daunting.
-But still--
-Of course, it's daunting.
Most certainly.
Advertisement planning is no joke.
If every Tom, Dick, and Harry could do it,
then why would our marketing team exist?
Don't you agree?
-Yes.
-Of course.
What's wrong? Are you insulted?
Your loser team
was just for show from the start!
You should just focus on
changing those diapers
and pulling out those weeds at the park.
How dare you covet
someone else's livelihood?
"Loser team"?
"Every Tom, Dick, and Harry"?
-Have you lost your damn mind?
-Calm down, Nan-suk.
What did you say? Why this lady…
Do you think we're in a market
where the loudest person wins?
This is a workplace!
You should be competing with your skills!
Yes!
That's correct!
That's why we're doing
a competitive pitch, are we not?
What?
Forget your title in the hierarchy,
which team you're on,
and whose inner circle you belong to.
Is there anything better
than a competitive pitch
to truly assess skill?
Right?
-But that's--
-She's right!
We're trying to compete with our skills,
so what's the issue?
Maybe they're scared of losing
their livelihoods to the loser team.
What? Scared?
That must be it.
Why would I be scared of stay-at-home moms
whose only experience is changing diapers?
You should
be scared.
Stay-at-home moms
are the key demographic
the marketing team should be winning over.
Now, those very ladies
are getting involved directly.
-Right?
-Right.
Right.
Enjoy the rest of your meal then.
-Shall we get going now?
-Yes.
-I'm done eating.
-Let's go.
-My goodness.
Why those…
I ought to just…
Is the pressure still too much?
Screw the pressure or whatever.
I can't contain this anger inside me.
Do you still want to go weeding
in the park?
No.
Forget the weeds.
I want to pull Ma's hair out.
And you, Go-eun?
Do you find the big budget intimidating?
Screw it.
Sink or swim, we need to go for it.
You've all heard of
this saying before, right?
Those who seek death shall live,
and those who seek life shall die.
Let's go!
-You're right.
-Something like this.
I agree.
Here you go.
Okay.
Found it!
This is it.
Look at this. Right here.
AN EYE-CATCHING AD COPY
SHOW WHY PLANTING TREES BENEFITS OUR KIDS!
KEYWORDS: TREE, HEALTH, LOVE
We're done!
-Finally!
-It looks amazing!
-You haven't eaten yet, right?
-Oh my gosh!
A GREEN FUTURE WE DRAW TOGETHER
GROWING UP MEANS BECOMING STRONGER
WITHOUT ANYONE NOTICING
We brought tteokbokki and fried sides!
-Let's eat.
-No, stop!
-Not here.
-I'll take them over there.
-Yeah.
Where are the plates again?
Over here.
The concept looks good.
A GREEN FUTURE WE DRAW TOGETHER
The copies are also excellent.
The sample shoot
is all we have left now, right?
Have you contacted the photographer?
Yes. He agreed to do it.
I set up a meeting as well.
Okay. Great.
What? Where are you going to work?
Have you lost your mind?
I mean, the offer was too good
to turn down.
A big corporate project
would also look good on my resume.
I mean, who am I to tell you what to do?
I don't want to
stand in the way of your career.
But just thinking about it
is suffocating.
Maybe my being there
could help you ease up a bit.
If everyone knows I'm your husband,
it'll clear up all the doubts.
But that won't be the case, will it?
I feel like our awkward acting
will just give it all away.
"Awkward acting"?
Did you forget I played Romeo
in my high school drama club?
The competition
was a whopping 12 to 1 back then.
Don't worry about my acting skills.
Just look at yourself.
How could I not worry?
You must've lost your mind!
You'd better stay on your toes,
or we're both done for.
-You hear me?
-Don't worry about my acting skills!
I seriously can't believe you!
What?
Hello.
Hey!
Hold on.
What is it?
Let's just stay here for a bit.
-The elevator's here. Let's go.
-Hey!
Please hold the door!
You could've just dropped her off
at the building entrance.
She's not a child, you know.
I'm also on my way to work.
Here.
I have a meeting with Mr. Kang Gyeong-min.
Why would you meet with Mr. Kang?
I look forward to working with you.
I'm Kim Seon-u.
My wife told me what you did.
I don't know how to thank you.
We'll pay you back as soon as we can.
Forget the money.
Were you aware
of just how much danger she was in?
She was, wasn't she?
My wife can be quite stubborn.
I told her repeatedly
that I'd come pick her up,
but she stopped me because she didn't know
when she'd be done with work.
We actually had our first fight
as a married couple because of that.
-"First"?
-Yes, our first.
Oh, I see.
You've never fought before.
My friend fought with his wife,
and his wife even ran away to Jeju
for a few days.
That would never happen with us.
My Rim can't even sleep
without me by her side.
Excuse me.
Where's Mr. Gong Ji-hyeok's office?
He's in the middle of a meeting right now.
Do you have an appointment?
It's fine.
I don't need to make one to see him.
Mr. Gong, you have a guest.
Thanks,
honey.
"Honey"?
Hey, Ha-yeong.
What brings you here?
I came by because I heard
you were having your first meeting.
Deputy Director Yu was the one
who introduced Mr. Kim to me.
And this is
a member of my team and Mr. Kim's wife,
Ms. Go Da-rim.
It's nice to meet you. I'm Go Da-rim.
You're his wife?
-His wife?
-Ms. Yu?
There's a work matter
I'd like to discuss with you.
We're going to step out for a quick chat.
-Sure.
-Let's go.
Come with me.
Please excuse us.
Let's go.
I mean, still,
how could you pretend to be married?
Wait.
Just hold on.
Her mother practically saved my life.
I knew it was wrong, but I had to help.
Could you keep this a secret?
Please.
So you're saying
this is for her mother's sake
and not for her sake, right?
Right.
Then that means you two are definitely,
certainly, positively, absolutely
just friends, right?
Yes.
That's quite an unfortunate situation,
but my conscience will simply not allow me
to overlook a crime.
However, I could turn a blind eye
depending on how you do.
What do I need to do?
I'll do anything. Just say the word.
If it makes you uncomfortable,
I could tell my husband to quit.
I'm fine.
If anyone is uncomfortable, it'd be you.
Unlike someone, I don't have a partner,
nor have I done anything wrong.
I'm very relaxed.
You must be worried
I'll snitch to your husband.
But don't worry.
Meddling in my team members'
personal affairs…
is not my cup of tea.
I didn't mean it like that,
but thank you anyway.
If I say I'll forget it, I forget it.
A mistake.
A sort of accident.
A game of ping-pong with a stranger.
I don't even remember such things.
I see.
He remembers every single thing.
What a small world we live in.
Who knew you'd be Ms. Go's husband?
You two make such a great couple.
-The perfect-looking couple.
-My thoughts exactly.
And you two sort of resemble one another.
We've been friends since we were kids.
I guess we've grown
to resemble one another
after all those long years.
How did you go
from being childhood friends
to lovers, and then, partners?
Well, you see, what happened was…
It was just--
I didn't know at first
because we were longtime friends,
but I eventually realized
that I had fallen for her.
And I had fallen for her hard.
It was one-sided for a while,
but when I saw her with someone else,
I couldn't stand it anymore.
So I confessed.
Why am I getting butterflies?
Are you sure you've been married
for seven years?
Sorry about that.
-What was that for?
-You just flew.
That's enough chit-chat.
This is Deputy Director Yu Ha-yeong
from Taeyu Art Hall.
She'll be organizing
a photography exhibition
in association with this campaign.
Hello.
We've decided to take part
because we liked the campaign's objective.
We especially plan to support Mr. Kim
as much as we can,
so please let me know
if you ever need anything.
Then could you provide support
for the ad concept shoot
for the presentation?
We might need to go on a business trip
for some on-site shooting.
Of course.
We'll cover all expenses,
wherever it may be.
We'll even cover an overnight trip.
Applause.
-Hey.
-Yeah?
You're a pretty good actor.
I almost thought you really liked me.
Did you?
How did you come up
with such a love story on the spot?
Oh, Romeo!
Do you feel more relaxed now?
Yeah.
Thanks, my friend.
Babe, I'll see you at home later.
-Okay.
-Ms. Go Da-rim.
You don't have to do that in front--
The elevator!
It's here.
SHH, IT'S A SECRET!
-Why did you cut me off?
-Well…
Ms. Yu.
Since you said you'd keep it a secret,
can you just pretend you don't know
in front of Da-rim as well?
Why? You don't need to act in front of me.
She may not look it,
but she's really soft-hearted and timid.
If she knows you know,
it'll only make her nervous
and get her to mess up.
So I'd appreciate it
if we could just keep it between us.
How incredibly considerate of you.
-Then make time for me today.
-Today?
I thought of something I want to do.
Take my first birthday photos.
Fill this out for me.
What's this?
You just have to write down things
that make you smile.
Things that make me smile?
FIDE, BABIES, HORSEBACK RIDING,
ACOUSTIC GUITAR,
BEETHOVEN, QUOKKAS, A KIND AND WARM PERSON
All right.
Should we have a little chat?
How's my pose?
First time riding one?
I've been riding horses since I was 6.
How did it feel
when you first rode one?
It was really fun.
I was really good at connecting
with my horse.
My horse is so cute. I miss it.
Where is it now?
In Jeju Island.
They're all so cute. I miss them so much.
Why did you want
a first birthday photoshoot?
Don't you already have photos from then?
I don't. My parents were always busy.
When I was little,
I was almost always alone.
Well, the housekeeper was there.
That's why I thought
I should at least take them now.
They're all pretty similar.
I don't know what to choose.
Can I see that for a second?
I think…
this one, this one,
and this one are the best.
Oh, really?
You think so?
Yes, they're pretty.
Why?
Why are they pretty?
You're smiling.
You really look like a baby
when you smile big like that.
Since this is
my first birthday photoshoot,
I'll go with the ones
where I look like a baby.
Okay.
Then, this one, this one, and this one.
I'll print those three for you.
We're done, right?
No, not yet.
I want to make an album.
The one that carries 22 photos.
I have a reservation coming up.
I'm not taking them all today.
I'll decide the time, location,
and concept.
You just need to show up
and take the pictures.
That means we have 19 more to go.
You already know, right?
-Guys, hold on.
-If you all have kids, you already know.
-Of course.
-Big movements.
-Movements need to be big.
-Yes, that's right.
We're going with an eco-friendly concept.
-Yes, that's what we're going for.
-That's right.
Come this way!
Amazing! Keep going!
That's it!
Keep going!
Who wants to follow these?
Who wants to follow me?
Who wants to catch them?
Let's take a short break.
-Okay.
-Let's take a break, kids.
Let's go and take a break.
Kids.
Kim Seon-u.
-That's great.
-Don't take my picture.
It's nice. Keep going.
Take a look.
-What is that?
-It came out well.
You're pretty cool today. A total pro.
That's nothing new.
You've seen me work before.
But still, it's definitely different
seeing you outside of the studio.
-Hold on.
-What?
You have something here.
Thanks.
Then take a pretty shot of me.
Try jumping.
That's good.
Have some more fun.
Oh, me?
-You call that just being friends?
-Hold on.
Mr. Kim, let's eat before we continue.
The air is no good here.
Let's go.
-Mother!
-TF!
Good job today.
-Good work today.
-Well done.
-That's refreshing.
-My goodness, that's good.
It's been forever
since I've had such a feast.
It feels like it's my birthday.
It'll be my treat today,
-so please enjoy to your heart's content.
-Will do.
-Thank you.
It's been years since I've eaten out
without having to look after the kids.
What do you say
to just one business trip every week?
Should we?
-Da-rim, there's no meat there.
-Yeah?
-Nan-suk, this is so tasty.
-Is it?
-Abalones.
-Thank you.
Thank you.
Mr. Kim, you should eat too.
You worked the hardest today,
but you're only taking care of your wife.
Sorry, it's just become a habit.
Eat up, honey.
Honey…
You too, honey.
They're just overflowing with love.
I saw it earlier during the shoot too.
Where can you even find
a husband like that?
When a husband treats his wife
as well as he does,
it's for one of two reasons.
Number one, he's not human. He's an angel.
Or number two, he has a huge secret
he's hiding from his wife.
What could he be hiding?
It's not like he's cheating on her.
Of course.
He's totally an angel. That's it.
-I'm an angel?
-Of course.
That's not true.
The real angel
is right here.
-Forget it. Let's just drink.
-Drink up.
-What did I just see? Jeez.
-Unbelievable.
Drink up, Nan-suk.
Jeez.
How pretty.
This is the perfect weather
for a first birthday photoshoot.
Ms. Yu?
I thought this floral background
would be perfect.
Right now?
Yes, I decide the time,
location, and concept.
And you take the pictures, no matter what.
That was our agreement, no?
That's right.
I'm getting tipsy.
I need some fresh air.
Da-rim, where are you going?
I just need some fresh air.
Have a drink with me when you come back.
-Okay.
-You drank too much, huh?
Is Da-rim a lightweight?
I don't think so.
Look at her pretending!
Goodness, Mr. Gong!
I must pour you a drink.
I need to have a heart-to-heart with you.
Bottoms up.
What a man.
You need to pour me one too, Mr. Gong.
Thank you.
-Gosh, it looks so tasty.
-Me too!
-Me too.
I really need to use the bathroom.
Good.
That's good.
-How are they?
-Just a moment.
They're coming out a bit dark.
Let's do it next time
with better lighting.
Okay.
Let's go.
You'll need to share a room
with Ms. Go tonight.
Will you be okay?
Yes, I'll be fine.
We've been friends for over 20 years.
That's why it's unsafe…
I mean, more uncomfortable.
How about you come out later?
I'll get you another room.
-You don't have to do--
-I don't like it.
Where is she?
Jeez.
What's going on? Are they fighting?
Here you are, Mr. Gong.
Oh, you must've also needed some fresh--
DYNAMITE KISS
What's with you? You look like someone
who desperately needs the bathroom.
Did you two come together?
You sure about this?
-It makes it thrilling.
-Naughty boy.
They both must've lost their minds.
What do you think of me as a man?
Ji-hyeok, I have a crush on someone.
I saw you and Kim Seon-u kissing.
This is driving me crazy.
Ms. Go is just an ordinary woman
and mother.
Why are you even worried about her?
Because she's my team member.
Subtitle translation by: Justin Kim